I think it's been hard,
Hell and heaven
What I see in front of me is incomprehension,
Ignorance and confusion I would say.
Hard, it has been confusing,
And it has been depressed.
Unspoken, tough but finally so
was actually very good
When I think back on my schooling
so has it been like a prison
It's been a waste of time to go
Especially no and math ... I didn't understand anything
of what she was talking about.
It was like she
Talked extraterrestrial type.
To let a dyslexic go ahead and read aloud
Or write something on the board, it's really
walked scary like hedging him down in a
Diving equipment with sharks.
It's so heavenly
Nervous because you can't read aloud that way.
I can't write, I can't spell
In concrete terms, with a regular pen.
In high school it is that you have to choose information.